<u>Ranjeet Kumar</u>

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



Betonova Ulica-21, Kranj -4000



https://ranjeet2311.github.io/

www.linkedin.com/in/ranjeet-kumar-23n19



Ranjeetkumar2311@gmail.com



+386 696-389-45



About me

I am a self-taught Web developer with a strong understanding of HTML, CSS, SAAS, JAVA SCRIPT and BOOTSTRAP. I work with these technologies on a daily basis, and I also have loads of personal projects to demonstrate that knowledge. Working hard is very much a part of my personal identity. I love my pace of life and would bring all the interpersonal and time management skills that are such a core part of my work life to this role.

I imagine a project and draw it on the paper and implement with the help of HTML, CSS and JS. I remember when I made my first website, I was so excited about couldn't stop clicking that button and since then I didn't look back and kept on working on my skills and understanding of web development and web designing.

My zeal to learn more and more brings me always on a bigger challenge, as I started my journey with WordPress development and I used to do little bit of code changes according to my need, that was the beginning to this point where I make everything on my own for my projects.

Life has been a long journey of a constant learning.

For more details, please visit my GitHub (profile link is mentioned above)

Work Experience

• Work Experience at "Soft Smart Services" Digital Services | Aug 2015 - Present |

<u>Responsibilities:</u> It's my business where I do designing and developing dynamic Websites, Ecommerce Websites using WordPress, Magento, Open Cart, Woo-Commerce.

Dealing with USA/CA clients, answering questions related to project development.

• Work Experience at "In Technologies" | Apr 2013 - 2014 |

<u>Responsibilities:</u> Customer support, attending calls from USA/CA/Britain. Answering queries, helping them with basic software troubleshooting.

• Work Experience at "Ace Global" | Apr 2012 - Apr 2013 |

<u>Responsibilities:</u> Making new customers for Optus telecom (Australia), verifying contracts and helping customers to move to Optus telecom from their present provider.

• Work Experience at "One Touch Solution" | Feb 2011 - 2012 |

<u>Responsibilities:</u> Working on the behalf of TRUenergy (Australia), making new contracts with new clients. Giving clients a calculative idea on why to move from present company to new TRUenergy.

Education

- Primary School: GBSSS Moti Nagar, New Delhi
- Secondary School: GBSSS Moti Nagar, New Delhi
- <u>Senior Secondary School</u>: GBSSS, Rajouri Garden, New Delhi
- <u>University</u>: University of Delhi

Skills

Core Technologies



Thank You!